I remember when I was like really trying to pursue music
and was like, okay, I'm gonna rap, I'm gonna sing.
And everybody was discouraging me
because they were like, no, you can't do both.
You can't do both, you can't do both.
And it was not because other people hadn't done both.
It was because they didn't know how to market that
or they didn't know how to make that kind of music.
And so it really put a seed of doubt inside of me
that I could figure it out
because they couldn't figure it out.
And looking back, I just, I'm like, yo,
you really were listening to a bunch of cowards.
You were listening to a bunch of cowards.
Why are they cowards though, Amanda?
Why they gotta be all that?
They're cowards because they were projecting
their own things on me.
They're projecting they shit onto me.